A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Office of the President, Office Files of McGeorge Bundy FA617
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appendix A: Reports
  - Bundy, McGeorge. Memorandum for the Trustees, 1974 June (Report 10928)
  - Bundy, McGeorge. Memorandum on the Size of the Board of Trustees, 1972 November (Report 10925)
  - Bundy, McGeorge. Merrimon Cuniggim's Work and Our Response -- A Summary Report, 1975 June (Report 9185)
  - Bundy, McGeorge. Preliminary Budget Planning for 1970 and Beyond, 1969 March (Report 3464)
  - Bundy, McGeorge. Remarks to the Staff of the Ford Foundation (Report 10923)
  - Bundy, McGeorge. Remarks to the Staff of the Ford Foundation, 1974 December (Report 9193)
  - Bundy, McGeorge. A Response to the Trustees on Proposed Priorities, Special Questions, and Remaining Hard Choices, 1976 November (Report 3450)
  - Bundy, McGeorge. Special "Fund for Michigan" -- Progress Report, 1974 June (Report 10929)
  - Bundy, McGeorge. Statement by McGeorge Bundy President, The Ford Foundation before the Subcommittee on Communications Committee on Commerce..., 1966 August (Report 10920)
  - Bundy, McGeorge. Statement of McGeorge Bundy President of the Ford Foundation before House Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1967 July (Report 10922)
  - Bundy, McGeorge. Statement by McGeorge Bundy President, before the Subcommittee on Commerce, 1967 April (Report 10921)
  - Bundy, McGeorge. Statement by McGeorge Bundy, President of the Ford Foundation to the Committee on Ways and Means, 1969 February (Report 10880)
  - Bundy, McGeorge. [Travel and Study Awards... to Certain Members of the Staff of the Late Senator Robert F. Kennedy], 1968 August (Report 10903)
  - Bundy, McGeorge. Two Years Ahead: Ford Foundation Programs for 1974 and 1975, 1973 (Report 4744)
  - Carroll, Joan. Recruiting and Affirmative Action Report: Professional Staff: FY 1976, 1976 October (Report 10904)
  - Chafkin, Sol. Four Years of Program Related Investments and Some Issues for the Future, 1972 (Report 11035)
  - Cheit, Earl F. Notes on the Financial Problems of Colleges and Universities, 1972 (Report 11080)
  - Colebrooke, Beatrice. Report on the Findings of Concerned Minority Women Regarding the Internal Policies and Practices of the Ford Foundation, 1972 June (Report 10889)
  - Collins, Norman R. Gangetic Basin: Notes on Resource Management Issues, 1977 October (Report 10965)
  - Collins, Norman R. Notes for Village Visits in Bihar and Uttar Pradesh, 1977 October (Report 10964)
  - Committee on Citizen in World Affairs. Report of Committee on Citizen Education in World Affairs, 1965 February (Report 2581)
  - Conway, Gordon. Proposal for an Environment Research Training Project on Land and Water Resource Development at Institut Pertaninan Bogor (IPB), 1974 September (Report 10979)
  - Council on Library Resources. Council on Library Resources: A Review of Its Work (Report 2536)
  - Cox, Brenda. Instructional Television at the College Level - A Summary of Present Trends, 1966 June (Report 10945)
  - Crossland, Fred E. Minority Participation in American Higher Education Taking Stock of Progress and Charting the Course Ahead, 1978 June (Report 9753)
  - Cuninggim, Merrimon. Affirmative Action, 1975 April (Report 11001)
  - Cuninggim, Merrimon. "The Crisis in Philanthropy", 1975 October (Report 11000)
  - Cuninggim, Merrimon. The Foundation's People and Their Work, 1975 February (Report 11002)
  - Cuninggim, Merrimon. Grant-Judging in the Ford Foundation, 1975 December (Report 11004)
  - Cuninggim, Merrimon. Grants to Individuals, 1974 June (Report 10998)
  - Cuninggim, Merrimon. An Independent View of Dependent Organizations of the Ford Foundation, 1975 January (Report 11003)
  - Cuninggim, Merrimon. [Memoranda to McGeorge Bundy], 1975 (Report 10996)
  - Cuninggim, Merrimon. Relations with Other Foundations, 1974 August (Report 10999)
  - Cuninggim, Merrimon. Report on a Trip to Ford Offices in Asia, 1974 February (Report 10997)
  - de Spoelberch, Guillaume. Investment Planning in Egypt, 1977 (Report 11052)
  - Dodds, R. Harcourt NAACP/Mississippi Boycott Case - Status Report, 1976 (Report 11078)
  - Dressner, Howard R. Copyright and Publishing Guidelines, 1974 (Report 11032)
  - Dressner, Howard R. External Affirmative Action Initiative, 1973 September (Report 10935)
  - Dressner, Howard R. Fiduciary Responsibility of Trustees for Investments, 1976 May (Report 9207)
  - Dressner, Howard R. My Trip to Asia (February 14-March 17), 1973 (Report 11031)
  - Drake-Beam and Associates. Attitude Survey Concerning the Role of Women at the Ford Foundation, 1970 December (Report 6002)
  - Dye, Richard W. Academia de Humanismo Cristiano, 1976 (Report 11047)
  - Dye, Richard W. Adjusting to Reduced Spending Levels, 1974 June (Report 2477)
  - Edley, Christopher. Civil Rights: The Negro Movement for Equal Opportunity, 1965 March (Report 1263)
  - Edwards, Robert H. The Foundation in Lebanon: July 1976, 1966 July (Report 8892)
  - Edwards, Robert H. Saudi Arabia, 1977 (Report 11051)
  - Finklestein, David. Sino-American Cultural Exchange, 1973 (Report 11057)
  - Firstenberg, Paul. Program-Related Investments, 1972 (Report 11034)
  - Ford Foundation. Adolescence: From Exploration to Program, 1976 November (Report 9204)
  - Ford Foundation. The Affirmative Action Personnel Program, 1973 (Report 7754)
  - Ford Foundation. Agriculture - Mexico (Report 10970)
  - Ford Foundation. Background Paper for the Discussion to be held at the Ford Foundation on Tuesday, May 24, 1966 (Report 11044)
  - Ford Foundation. [Columbia] General Background Information, 1970 (Report 10960)
  - Ford Foundation. Comments and Recommendations of the Ford Foundation on the Proposed Regulations Under the Health Maintenance Organization Act of 1973 (Report 11036)
  - Ford Foundation. Communications Law, Research and Public Policy, 1969 March (Report 1366)
  - Ford Foundation. The Congress for Cultural Freedom, 1966 June (Report 10893)
  - Ford Foundation. Chronology [of Events in Lebanon] (Report 11050)
  - Ford Foundation. Dealing with the "Hard" Political Cases: UAR Kenya Meeting of Representatives, 1968 June (Report 2917)
  - Ford Foundation. Dependent Organizations, 1971 (Report 4575)
  - Ford Foundation. Deterioration of Educational Standards in Asia and Africa. Kenya Meeting of Representatives, 1968 June (Report 2933)
  - Ford Foundation. Development of Local Competence. Kenya Meeting of Representatives, 1968 June (Report 3740)
  - Ford Foundation. Development of the Science & Engineering Program (Report 11041)
  - Ford Foundation. Education - Mexico (Report 10971)
  - Ford Foundation. External Affirmative Action Program, 1975 October (Report 2196)
  - Ford Foundation. External Affirmative Action Program, 1977 October (Report 6125)
  - Ford Foundation. Education and Development Agenda Papers, 1973 November (Report 2344)
  - Ford Foundation. The Ford Foundation and "Dependent" Organizations. An Information Paper, 1971 September (Report 2109)
  - Ford Foundation. Ford Foundation Salaries: A Study of Ford Foundation Senior Officer Salaries (Report 10993)
  - Ford Foundation. The Foundation's Responsibilities to New York City: Four Alternative Means of Payment, 1968 January (Report 1401)
  - Ford Foundation. Future Investment and Spending Policies, 1977 March (Report 3694)
  - Ford Foundation. International Portofolio Diversification, 1978 March (Report 5069)
  - Ford Foundation. Ford Foundation Meeting on Arms Control and International Security, 1974 July (Report 3413)
  - Ford Foundation. Ford Foundation Trustees' Site Visit to Baltimore, 1978 June (Report 4538)
  - Ford Foundation. The Foundation's Concerns with Peace and International Security, 1974 September (Report 9199)
  - Ford Foundation. How Foundations Can Avoid Crippling Legislation: 1969 (Report 10881)
  - Ford Foundation. The Government, The Universities and Research: A Report on a Conversation Among University Presidents, 1977 November (Report 6476)
  - Ford Foundation. Human Rights and Intellectual Freedom. Information Paper, 1975 November (Report 8610)
  - Ford Foundation. International Programs Related to the Status, Roles, and Opportunities of Women, 1975 November (Report 2066)
  - Ford Foundation. Issues in Rice Research, 1977 October (Report 10963)
  - Ford Foundation. The Kaysen Report on the Foundation and Arms Control, 1973 December (Report 2447)
  - Ford Foundation. Kenya Meeting of Representatives, Agenda Paper Session V: Languages and Linguistics, 1968 June (Report 10956)
  - Ford Foundation. Kenya Meeting of Representatives, Agenda Paper Session VII: An Optimistic Look at the Brain Drain, 1968 June (Report 10954)
  - Ford Foundation. The Management of College and University Resources, 1968 (Report 11053)
  - Ford Foundation. Metropolitan Opera Association, 1978 June (Report 4840)
  - Ford Foundation. Mexico - 1974 (Report 10972)
  - Ford Foundation. A National Environmental Research Institute, 1969 October (Report 10892)
  - Ford Foundation. New York City's Crisis: Background and Implications for the Ford Foundation, 1975 December (Report 3365)
  - Ford Foundation. Our Finances and Our Future Revisited, 1974 December (Report 9201)
  - Ford Foundation. Our Finances and Our Future Revisisted, 1974 December (Report 9192)
  - Ford Foundation. Past and Present Foundation Funded Research on Race and Ethnicity, 1973 August (Report 3701)
  - Ford Foundation. Pay as You Earn Staff Papers on Income Contingent Lending, 1971 June (Report 1917)
  - Ford Foundation. Population - Mexico (Report 10973)
  - Ford Foundation. Production Technology. Kenya Meeting of Representatives, 1968 June (Report 1602)
  - Ford Foundation. Report on Affirmative Action, 1979 March (Report 4117)
  - Ford Foundation. Report on Organized Crime Conference, 1976 October 25 - 26 (Report 6554)
  - Ford Foundation. Reproductive Biological Research Federal University of Bania, Brazil, 1970 (Report 11046)
  - Ford Foundation. Resource Bases for Development. Kenya Meeting of Representatives, 1968 June (Report 2886)
  - Ford Foundation. The Shrinking Gap, 1970 [?] (Report 10986)
  - Ford Foundation. Southern Africa, 1970s (Report 11048)
  - Ford Foundation. Special Program in Education, 1963 September (Report 2221)
  - Ford Foundation. Support for Experimental Projects of Public Interest Legal Representation by the Ford Foundation, 1970 July (Report 10897)
  - Ford Foundation. The United Negro College Fund, 1967 (Report 11086)
  - Ford Foundation. University Programs of Training and Research in Public Policy Studies, 1971 December (Report 2958)
  - Ford Foundation. Veterans, Deserters, and Draft-Evaders: the Vietnam Decade, 1974 September (Report 4133)
  - Ford Foundation. Vietnam: Veterans, Deserters, and Draft-Evaders, 1974 September (Report 10901)
  - Ford Foundation. Working Their Way to Work: A Discussion of Supported Work and the Role of Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation, 1974 (Report 11076)
  - Ford Foundation. Ad hoc Committee on Racial Policy Issues. Racial Policy Issues: Summary of Discussion and Recommendations, 1976 (Report 10883)
  - Ford Foundation. Advisory Management Committee. Reduction of Net Operating Cost of Foundation Food Services, 1975 April (Report 10885)
  - Ford Foundation. Advisory Management Committee. Report and Recommendations of the Subcommittee [on the Library], 1975 May (Report 10886)
  - Ford Foundation. Advisory Management Committee. Report of Subcommittee on Travel and Expenses, 1975 April (Report 10887)
  - Ford Foundation. Affirmative Action. Background Material: Affirmative Action, 1977 February (Report 10888)
  - Ford Foundation. Affirmative Action. Background Material Affirmative Action. Prepared for the Meeting of the Affirmative Action Advisory Committee, 1975 July (Report 2034)
  - Ford Foundation. Affirmative Action. Background Material Affirmative Action. Prepared for the Affirmative Action Committee, Revised 1977 March (Report 8007)
  - Ford Foundation. Affirmative Action. Report of the Subcommittee on Affirmative Action, 1975 December (Report 3129)
  - Ford Foundation. Affirmative Action. Report of the Subcommittee on Training for the Affirmative Action Advisory Committee, 1977 February (Report 8010)
  - Ford Foundation. Asia & Pacific. A Note on the Foundation's Program Concerned with Women in Development, 1977 (Report 10968)
  - Ford Foundation. Cairo Office Staff. The Ford Foundation in Egypt 1975: Where Do We Go from Here?, 1975 June (Report 4597)
  - Ford Foundation. Com. on Public Policy & Social Org. Americans and the Middle East, 1975 March (Report 8660)
  - Ford Foundation. Co-ordinating Committee on Women's Programs. Ford Foundation Co-ordinating Committee on Women's Programs: Annual Report to the President, 1975 January (Report 5583)
  - Ford Foundation. Co-ordinating Committee on Women's Programs. Ford Foundation Co-ordinating Committee on Women's Programs: Annual Report to the President, 1976 July (Report 2945)
  - Ford Foundation. Co-ordinating Committee on Women's Programs. Ford Foundation Co-ordinating Committee on Women's Programs: Annual Report to the President, 1978 June (Report 4439)
  - Ford Foundation. Division of National Affairs. The Energy Policy Project. A Report to the Trustees on Planning and Organization, 1972 March (Report 2125)
  - Ford Foundation. Division of National Affairs. National Affairs' Programs: Some Comments on Background and Rationale, 1975 November (Report 6510)
  - Ford Foundation. Division of National Affairs. Program Status and Preliminary Planning Paper, 1974 March (Report 10984)
  - Ford Foundation. Division of National Affairs. Recommendations for Women's Programs, 1971 October (Report 2659)
  - Ford Foundation. Division of National Affairs. Resources and Environment. Excerpt from a Report to the Trustees, 1969 December (Report 4798)
  - Ford Foundation. Economic Development & Administration. Program in Economic Development and Administration: EDA Grants 1956-1965 (Report 11081)
  - Ford Foundation. Education and Research. Children's Television Workshop, 1972 June (Report 9144)
  - Ford Foundation. Education and Research. Education Activities of the Ford Foundation. Proposed Program and Budget for FY 1980 and FY 1981, 1978 (Report 9114)
  - Ford Foundation. Education and Research. Education and Research, 1967 October (Report 10938)
  - Ford Foundation. Education and Research. Education and Research Division: Program Actions in Fiscal Year 1967, 1967 November (Report 10937)
  - Ford Foundation. Education and Research. Future Program Choices in Education and Research [Further Comment], 1975 June (Report 10936)
  - Ford Foundation. Education and Research. Future Program--Education and Research Division, 1975 June (Report 2257)
  - Ford Foundation. Education and Research. Higher Education for Under-Represented Minorities, 1970 January (Report 2846)
  - Ford Foundation. European and International Affairs. Arms Control and International Security: A Need for University Centers?, 1972 October (Report 10890)
  - Ford Foundation. International Division. The Ford Foundation International Division Conference, 1971 October (Report 9830)
  - Ford Foundation. International Division. [Nigeria], 1970 (Report 10961)
  - Ford Foundation. International Division. Research, Scholarship, and Cultural Development, 1975 July (Report 9828)
  - Ford Foundation. International Division. Visit to Indonesia October 15-19, 1977: Briefing Book, 1977 October (Report 10995)
  - Ford Foundation. International Division. Working Paper for Third Meeting on Education and Development, 1975 July (Report 6528)
  - Ford Foundation. Grants Payments Committee. Report of the Grant Payments Committee, 1974 November (Report 10884)
  - Ford Foundation. Middle East and Africa. Middle East Program Plans, 1976 March (Report 9210)
  - Ford Foundation. Office of the Arts. Office of the Arts, 1975 December (Report 10308)
  - Ford Foundation. Office of the Arts. Office of the Arts, 1975 June (Report 10294)
  - Ford Foundation. Office of the Chairman. The Ford Foundation Management and Program Trends in the Fifties and Sixties, 1971 June (Report 2802)
  - Ford Foundation. Office Resources & the Environment. Environmental Law. Ending Eight Years of General Support Grants, 1977 (Report 5184)
  - Ford Foundation. Office Resources & the Environment. Public Policy Analysis: The Brookings Institute and Resources for the Future, 1978 June (Report 4147)
  - Ford Foundation. Office Resources & the Environment. Resources and the Environment in the Developing Countries, 1976 March (Report 9208)
  - Ford Foundation. Self Group. Self Study Interviews, 1971 (Report 11088)
  - Ford Foundation. Telecommunications Task Force. Report of the Subcommittee on Education of The Telecommunications Task Force, 1973 July (Report 2734)
  - Fox, Melvin J. Language Activities in Relation to Budget Alternatives, 1974 July (Report 2963)
  - Friendly, Fred W. FY 1973 Budget, 1972 February (Report 6313)
  - Friendly, Fred W. Looking Toward FY 1974-75, 1972 February (Report 2459)
  - Friendly, Fred W. Preliminary Memorandum on Major Budget Issues, 1970 January (Report 10974)
  - Friendly, Fred W. Statement by Fred Friendly Advisor on Television, the Ford Foundation before Subcommittee on Communications..., 1966 August (Report 10950)
  - Friendly, Fred W. Statement of Fred W. Friendly Television Consultant to the Ford Foundation... Before the House Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1967 July (Report 10952)
  - Friendly, Fred W. Statement by Fred W. Friendly, The Ford Foundation before the Subcommittee on Communications Committee on Commerce, 1967 (Report 10949)
  - Gamble, William K. Foundation Program Strategy and the Resource-Rich LDCs, 1974 July (Report 4857)
  - Gant, George F. Resource Bases for Development. Comment on Agenda Paper. Kenya Meeting of Representatives, 1968 June (Report 9082)
  - Ginsberg, David. Testimony of David Ginsburg Counsel to the Ford Foundation before the House Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1967 July (Report 10951)
  - Goodwin, Crauford D. EIA Review of Brookings' Program of Foreign Policy Studies, 1971 (Report 11059)
  - Goodwin, Crauford D. Grants Program on the International Economic Order, 1974 (Report 11060)
  - Goodwin, Crauford D. An International Institute for Policy Research, 1976 August (Report 5079)
  - Goodwin, Crauford D. International Institute for Strategic Studies, 1975 (Report 11061)
  - Goodwin, Crauford D. The Overseas Development Council: A Ten-Year Review for the Ford Foundation, 1978 (Report 11070)
  - Goodwin, Crauford D. Program on the Future of the International Economic Order, 1976 February (Report 8845)
  - Goodwin, Crauford D. Progress Report on Program on the Future of the International Economic Order, 1974 June (Report 10983)
  - Gormbley, William P. Plan Administrator's 1978 Annual Report: Retirement and Thrift Plans (Report 10934)
  - Gormbley, William P. Retrenchment, 1979 (Report 11040)
  - Habte, Aklilu. Higher Education in Ethiopia in the 70's and Beyond (Report 2345)
  - Hagler, Jon L., Jay Light and Gary L. Bergstrom. Budget Policy, Investment Policy, and Uncertainty, 1977 December (Report 4138)
  - Hagler, Jon L. Investment Policies, Spending Policies & Uncertainties, 1977 June (Report 3287)
  - Hagler, Jon L. Material for 1978 Proxy Season, 1978 March (Report 10992)
  - Hardin, Lowell S. International Agricultural Centers and Related Issues, 1970 December (Report 10989)
  - Hathaway, Dale E. Notes on the World Food Situation - August 1974, 1974 August (Report 9200)
  - Heaps, David. Dealing with "Hard" Political Cases. Kenya Meeting of Representatives, 1968 June (Report 3608)
  - Heaps, David. French Government Relations in Vietnam, 1974 (Report 11067)
  - Heaps, David. 1980 Budget, 1974 July (Report 4310)
  - Hertz, Willard. Ford Foundation Board of Trustees Summary of Discussion on Foundation and Arms Control Studies, 1973 December (Report 10926)
  - Hertz, Willard. Grants for Capital Purposes, 1950-1974 (Report 11030)
  - Hertz, Willard. March 1978 Board of Trustees Meeting Summary of Discussion: Future Investment and Spending Policies, 1978 March (Report 10930)
  - Howe, Harold. Agenda for the Education Committee Meeting, 1973 March (Report 10941)
  - Howe, Harold. "...items, issues, and ideas..." in Response to Your January 14 Request, 1972 February (Report 2461)
  - Howe, Harold. Preliminary Comments on the Federal Budget for FY 1974, 1973 February (Report 5913)
  - Institutional Strategy Associates, Inc. Henry Ford Hospital Summary of Progress, 1976 September (Report 5707)
  - Institutional Strategy Associates, Inc. Report on Henry Ford Hospital, 1978 October (Report 2353)
  - Jaffe, Sanford M. Communications, 1968 (Report 11082)
  - Jones, William K. Electronic Communications: Public Policy Issues and Research Activities, 1967 October (Report 3735)
  - Katz, Abraham. Analysis Relating to FCC Inquiry on Domestic Satellites, 1967 February (Report 10946)
  - Katzowitz, Lauren. The Equal Rights Amendment: A Discussion, 1972 (Report 2641)
  - Kaysen, Carl. Recommendations for a National Program in Support of Research and Training in Arms Control and Related Subjects, 1973 July (Report 2447)
  - Kelly, Eamon M. New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation--My Nomination and Withdrawal, 1979 (Report 11033)
  - Kennedy, Roger G. Budget Policy, Investment Policy, Prudence and Risk, 1976 July (Report 4049)
  - Kennedy, Roger G. Budgets, Assets and Expectations, 1976 December (Report 3449)
  - Kennedy, Roger G. Budgets, Markets and Capital Resources, 1972 (Report 11023)
  - Kennedy, Roger G. Discussion on Payout and Budget Levels, 1973 January (Report 10976)
  - Kennedy, Roger G. The Dollars We Will Have Available, 1974 (Report 11028)
  - Kennedy, Roger G. The First Four Years, 1974 March (Report 2474)
  - Kennedy, Roger G. The Ford Foundation Corporate Social Responsibility and the Investment Process Policy, Principles and Procedures, 1973 (Report 11025)
  - Kennedy, Roger G. Foundation as an Investor, 1971 (Report 11022)
  - Kennedy, Roger G. Lessons of the Past Year, 1973 (Report 11026)
  - Kennedy, Roger G. Museum of Modern Art, 1977 (Report 11072)
  - Kennedy, Roger G. Notes on Great Britain and Western Europe, 1974 (Report 11029)
  - Kennedy, Roger G. Portofolio Decisions and Social Responsibility, 1974 (Report 11027)
  - Kennedy, Roger G. Portofolio Deployment Costs and Benefits, 1975 March (Report 10982)
  - Kennedy, Roger G. Prejudice Paper #1: the economy and investment policy, c. 1975 (Report 11019)
  - Kennedy, Roger G. Summary [of Investment Policy], 1972 (Report 11024)
  - Kessinger, Tom G. Background Note for Briefing on Bihar Politics and Society, A.N. Sinha Institute, Patna, 1977 October (Report 10966)
  - Kingsley, J. Donald. Resource Bases for Development. Comments on Agenda Paper. Kenya Meeting of Representatives, 1968 June (Report 9106)
  - Kofsky, Nathan M. Note on the Agricultural Situation in the Soviet Union and Mainland China, 1970 December (Report 10988)
  - Lasswell, Harold. Postscript to Bellagio, 1966 March (Report 10958)
  - LeMelle, Wilbert J. On Reviewing the Budget in the International Division, 1974 July (Report 2476)
  - Lewis, Stephen R. Visit to Cairo, January 26-February 3, 1976 (Report 11049)
  - Lowry, W. McNeil. Institute of Fine Arts, New York University, 1972 (Report 11075)
  - Lowry, W. McNeil. Recommendations Concerning Issues, Ideas and Program Areas for Planning and Exploration in FY 1974 and FY 1975, 1972 February (Report 2458)
  - McDaniel, Joseph M. Summary of Patman Report on Tax-Exempt Foundations, 1962 December (Report 10882)
  - Magat, Richard. [Public Relations, Public Understanding, Public Image], 1970 July (Report 10898)
  - Magat, Richard. The Ford Foundation and Rep. Patman, 1969 February (Report 108902)